{
  "Category": [
    {
      "id": "C",
      "questionset1": [
        {
          "time": 30,
          "total_marks": 30
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who pratika?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl g",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "a"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Who1 invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "b"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "c"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "a"
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "b"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "a"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "b"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "Who invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "b"
        }
      ],
      "questionset2": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who lkfjlft?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Who1 invented JavaScript?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "C++",
      "questionset1": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "C++?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "C++?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        }
      ],
      "questionset2": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "C++2?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "C++ ?",
          "answers": {
            "a": "Douglas Crockford",
            "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "c": "Brendan Eich",
            "d": "amir jadhav"
          },
          "answer": "d"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}